A Paw Patrol Christmas is a animation, family,
adventure film directed by Jamie Whitney.
Rubble is looking forward to Santa bringing him a new laser drill, but finds that
Santa has come down with a cold and can’t deliver any presents.
When Mayor Humdinger decides he’s going to the North Pole to take all the
gifts for himself, it’s up to the PAW Patrol to stop him.
Chase (voice), played by Luke Dietz.
Skye (voice), played by Lilly Bartlam.
Rubble (voice), played by Lucien Duncan-Reid.
Marshall (voice), played by Jesse Gervasi.
Lizzy (voice), played by Courtney Gilmour.
Ryder (voice), played by Kai Harris.
Paw Patrol (stylized as PAW Patrol) is a Canadian children's animated television series created by Keith
Chapman and produced by Spin Master Entertainment, with animation provided by Guru Studio.
In Canada, the series is primarily broadcast on TVOntario
as part of the TVOKids programing block.
TVO first ran previews of the show in August 2013.
The series premiered on Nickelodeon's Nick Jr.
in the United States on August 12, 2013.
The series focuses on a young boy named Ryder who leads a crew of
search and rescue dogs that call themselves the Paw Patrol.
They work together on missions to protect the shoreside
community of Adventure Bay and surrounding areas.
Each dog has a specific set of skills based on emergency services professions,
such as a firefighter, a police officer, and an aviation pilot.
They all reside in doghouses that transform into customized
vehicles or "pupmobiles" for their missions.
They are also equipped with special hi-tech backpacks called "pup
packs" that contain tools relating to their respective job.
Since its debut, the series has developed into a media franchise, generating millions of dollars in revenue from
toy sales for Spin Master and has increased the company's presence in the preschool toy market.
The franchise includes a feature film which released in August 2021, followed by a sequel, The Mighty Movie, on September 29, 2023, another upcoming sequel The Dino Movie,
set to be released on July 31, 2026, and a spin-off series based on one of the show's main characters titled Rubble & Crew which premiered in February 2023.
The show celebrated its 10th anniversary in 2023.
The show, and its associated products, have received a variety of awards and nominations from associations such
as the Academy of Canadian Cinema & Television and the Academy of Television Arts & Sciences.
The series is currently on its twelfth season, which began airing in July 2025.
In early February 2023, series creator Keith Chapman said in an interview with The Hollywood Reporter
magazine that the series could still be on television for another ten years or more.
The film explores themes of cartoon, rescue
mission, dog, rescue team, cartoon dog.